- Are you ready, kids?
- 孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- ♪ Ohh... ♪
- ♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
- ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
- ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
- ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
all: SpongeBob SquarePants!
- Ready?
所有：海绵宝宝！
- 准备好？
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
- SpongeBob
- 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
[laughing]
[笑]
♪ ♪
[waves crashing]
[海浪拍打]
[upbeat tropical music]
[欢快的热带音乐]
♪ ♪
- Batter up!
- 击球！
- [humming]
- [嗡嗡声]
♪ ♪
Ah!
啊!
Ah, oh.
啊，哦。
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
- I got it, I got it.
- 我明白了，我明白了。
- Wah!
- 哇！
- [slurping]
- [发出声音]
Whoo-hoo!
- [laughs]
呼呼！
- [笑]
[laughing and cheering]
[笑声和欢呼]
- [laughing]
- [笑]
- What are you two dizzy
dingbats doing out here?
- 你们两个晕什么啊
dingbats 在这里做什么？
- Just treasuring our time
together, Squidward.
- 只是珍惜我们的时间
一起，章鱼哥。
- Well, that time is over.
- 好吧，那段时间已经结束了。
Say good night,
go to your separate houses,
说晚安，
and be quiet!
保持安静！
[both whimpering]
[两人都呜咽]
- I can't do it!
- 我做不到！
I can't be away
from my best friend.
我不能离开
来自我最好的朋友。
- No, it hurts too much!
- 不，太痛了！
[both crying]
[两人都哭了]
- Oh, will you two
cut it out?
- 噢，你们两个愿意吗？
剪掉它吗？
- Cut it out...
- 剪掉它...
Squidward,
that's a great idea!
章鱼哥，
这是个好主意！
both: It is?
两人：是吗？
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- Wow!
- 哇！
My turn!
轮到我了！
[groans]
[呻吟]
[chuckles]
[笑声]
- [chuckles]
- [轻笑]
-[groans]
-[呻吟]
- Aww.
- 哇。
[both chittering]
[两人都叽叽喳喳]
- I think I'm gonna be sick.
- 我想我会生病的。
- Here you go, Patrick.
- 给你，帕特里克。
Now we never have
to be apart,
现在我们从来没有
分开，
even when
we're not together.
即使当
我们没有在一起。
- This is great.
- 这太棒了。
See you forever, SpongeBob.
永远再见，海绵宝宝。
- Yeah, see you forever,
Patrick.
- 是的，永远再见，
帕特里克.
[yawns]
[哈欠]
Time for bed, Tiny Patrick.
该睡觉了，小帕特里克。
- [cheering, laughing]
- [欢呼，大笑]
- [gurgling]
- [咯咯声]
- [indistinct shouting]
- [隐隐约约的喊叫]
[laughing]
[笑]
- [humming]
- [嗡嗡声]
[foghorn blares]
[雾号声]
- Hmm.
- 唔。
- [chuckles]
- [轻笑]
- Uh. Oh.
- 呃。哦。
- Ah.
- 啊。
[both laughing]
[两人都笑了]
- Ah!
- 啊！
[both snoring]
[两人都打呼噜]
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
Good morning, Squidward.
- Says who?
早上好，章鱼哥。
- 谁说的？
- [chuckles] You sit right
there, my hungry little sailor,
- [轻笑]你坐对了
在那里，我饥饿的小水手，
while I whip you up some grub
from the galley.
当我给你准备一些食物时
从厨房。
[both laugh]
[两人都笑了]
- Dah, uh-huh.
- 啊哈。
- [humming]
- [嗡嗡声]
- Ah.
- 啊。
[excited laughing]
[兴奋大笑]
Ahh.
啊。
Hmm?
唔？
[whimpers]
[呜咽]
Ahhh!
啊啊！
Yah!
啊！
[screaming]
[尖叫]
- Huh?
Careful there, little buddy.
- 啊？
小心一点，小伙伴。
The grill is hot.
烤架很热。
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
Ohhh.
噢。
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
[grunts]
[咕哝]
- [straining]
Huh?
- [紧张]
啊？
- Whee-ah!
- 呼啊！
- Stop!
- 停止！
Bad, Tiny Patrick.
坏了，小帕特里克。
Hmm.
唔。
Sorry to do this, little guy,
很抱歉这样做，小家伙，
but I have to keep you safe
while I get some work done.
但我必须保证你的安全
当我完成一些工作时。
- [whimpers]
- [呜咽]
- Ah-yah.
- 啊耶。
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
[whimpers]
[呜咽]
[snoring]
[打鼾]
[alarm blares]
[警报声]
[both yawn]
[两人都打哈欠]
- Good morning.
- 早上好。
- [excited cheer]
- [兴奋欢呼]
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
Aah.
啊。
[gulps]
[吞咽]
Didn't think I was gonna
be able to eat all that.
没想到我会
能够吃掉所有这些。
But then I did!
[chuckles]
但后来我做到了！
[笑声]
- [humming]
Brushy, brushy, brushy.
- [嗡嗡声]
刷毛，刷毛，刷毛。
- Come on, Tiny SpongeBob.
- 来吧，小海绵宝宝。
You gotta lift
with your back.
你得举起
和你的背。
- [straining]
- [紧张]
- Oh, oh.
Hey, SpongeBob.
- 哦，哦。
嘿，海绵宝宝。
- Patrick, hi.
- 帕特里克，嗨。
- Eeh.
- 呃。
Hmm. Hmm.
唔。唔。
- [grunts awkwardly]
- [尴尬地咕哝]
- [groans]
- [humming]
- [呻吟]
- [嗡嗡声]
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
[inhales deeply]
[深吸一口气]
- So, uh,
I'd love to hang out,
- 所以，呃，
我很想出去玩，
but I already have some plans
with Tiny Patrick here.
但我已经有了一些计划
和小帕特里克在这里。
- Oh, yeah, well,
me and Tiny SpongeBob,
- 哦，是的，好吧，
我和小海绵宝宝
we're pretty busy tonight,
so good night.
今晚我们很忙
晚安。
- Good night.
- 晚安。
- [straining,
frantic chittering]
- [紧张，
疯狂的叽叽喳喳]
- [upset chittering]
- [心烦意乱的叽叽喳喳声]
- I don't want you getting
into trouble during the night,
- 我不想让你得到
晚上遇到麻烦，
so you're gonna stay
in the aquarium
所以你会留下来
在水族馆里
like a good little
sleepy clam.
像一个好小
瞌睡的蛤蜊。
- Ahh!
- 啊！
[straining]
[紧张]
Ahhh!
啊啊！
[angry grunting]
[愤怒的咕哝]
- [grunting, straining]
- [咕哝，紧张]
- Huh? Hey.
- 啊？嘿。
Didn't you used to have
one, two...two arms?
你以前不是有过吗
一只、两只……两只手臂？
Okay, little buddy.
好吧，小伙伴。
Let's find that arm of yours.
让我们找到你的手臂。
Oh.
[grumbles]
哦。
[抱怨]
Nope.
没有。
Hmm.
唔。
Huh?
- Ah!
啊？
- 啊！
- Nope. Oh.
- 没有。哦。
Ah-ha!
I got it!
啊哈！
我得到了它！
- [whimpering]
- [呜咽]
[straining]
[紧张]
- I'll fix you up
in no time.
- 我会收拾你的
很快。
- [chittering]
- [叽叽喳喳]
- Good as new.
- 完好如新。
- Ehh.
Huh?
- 呃。
啊？
- Okay, good night.
- 好吧，晚安。
[snoring]
[打鼾]
- Huh?
- 啊？
[snapping]
[啪啪啪]
- [snoring]
- [打鼾]
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
- [snores]
- [打鼾]
[crickets chirping]
[蟋蟀鸣叫]
- [straining]
Oh?
- [紧张]
哦？
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[straining]
[紧张]
[groaning]
[呻吟]
Ding!
叮！
- [excited grunting]
- Yah!
- [兴奋的咕哝]
- 啊！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
- [snores, mumbles]
- [打鼾，咕哝]
Yes, Squidward,
extra mayo, I heard you.
是的，章鱼哥，
额外的蛋黄酱，我听到了。
[both whimper]
[两人都呜咽]
[both grumble]
[两人都抱怨]
- [groans softly]
- [轻声呻吟]
[confused grunts]
[困惑的咕哝声]
Oh, hi, Patrick.
哦，嗨，帕特里克。
- Hey, SpongeBob.
- 嘿，海绵宝宝。
- I don't remember us having
a sleepover last night.
- 我不记得我们有过
昨晚过夜。
[both grunting]
[两人都咕哝着]
[both cheering]
[两人欢呼]
- What's going on, SpongeBob?
- 发生什么事了，海绵宝宝？
- Oh, hey, little guys.
- 哦，嘿，小家伙们。
You're playing with each other.
So cute.
你们在互相玩耍。
太可爱了。
[both grumble]
[两人都抱怨]
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
[explosion]
[爆炸]
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
[groaning]
[呻吟]
- Whew.
- 呼。
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
both: Huh?
两人：啊？
[grumbling]
[抱怨]
- Ah, ah.
- 啊，啊。
[exciting chittering]
[激动人心的叽叽喳喳声]
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
-[straining]
-[紧张]
[grunts]
Hey!
[咕哝]
嘿！
[excited chittering]
[兴奋的叽叽喳喳声]
- What are they doing,
SpongeBob?
- 他们在做什么，
海绵宝宝？
- Just trying to live
their lives, Patrick.
- 只是想努力生活
他们的生活，帕特里克。
Just trying to live
their lives.
只是想努力生活
他们的生活。
Poor little guys.
可怜的小家伙们。
- [straining]
- [紧张]
- Our world is just too big
for them.
- 我们的世界太大了
对于他们来说。
Ohh, I have an idea.
哦，我有一个想法。
- Oh, I hope it's not
another one of your crazy plans
- 哦，我希望不是这样
你的另一个疯狂计划
to steal the Krappy Patty
secret formula.
偷克拉皮帕蒂
秘密配方。
- You're thinking
of Plankton, Patrick.
- 你在想
浮游生物，帕特里克。
- Oh, yeah!
- 哦，是的！
[both panting]
[两人都气喘吁吁]
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Ta-da!
- 哒哒！
A tiny home
for my tiny friend.
一个小家
为了我的小朋友。
- Ahh!
[chuckles]
- 啊！
[笑声]
- [happy gibberish]
- [快乐的胡言乱语]
- Oh, I get it.
- 哦，我明白了。
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- Nice work, Patrick.
Whoops!
- 干得好，帕特里克。
哎呀！
Almost forgot.
差点忘了。
You've got to have
a Gare-Bear.
你必须有
车站熊。
- Oh, yay!
- 哦，耶！
- Ohh. Huh?
- 哦。啊？
[chuckles]
[笑声]
both: Aww.
两人：哇哦。
- Hmm.
- 唔。
Hmm?
唔？
- Let's leave 'em alone,
Patrick.
- 让我们别打扰他们吧
帕特里克.
[both chittering]
[两人都叽叽喳喳]
- [straining]
- [紧张]
Ugh, too bright.
呃，太亮了。
[exciting chittering]
[激动人心的叽叽喳喳声]
Oh, those two again.
噢，又是那两个人。
What the--
什么是——
[groans]
[呻吟]
[excited chittering]
[兴奋的叽叽喳喳声]
Ow!
[grumbles]
噢！
[抱怨]
[both gasp]
[两人都喘气]
- No, get away.
Get away!
- 不，走开。
逃离！
[screaming]
[尖叫]